Every Wednesday. She meets him once per week.
Intimacy is a romance, drama, fantasy film directed by Patrice Chéreau.
Failed musician Jay abandoned his family and now earns a
living as head bartender in a trendy London pub.
Every Wednesday afternoon, a woman comes to his house
for graphic, almost wordless, sex.
One day, Jay follows her and learns about her.
This eventually disrupts their relationship.
Jay, played by Mark Rylance.
Claire, played by Kerry Fox.
Susan, Jay's wife, played by Susannah Harker.
Victor, played by Alastair Galbraith.
Ian, played by Philippe Calvario.
Andy, Claire's husband, played by Timothy Spall.
Intimacy is a 2001 erotic drama film directed by Patrice Chéreau from a screenplay he co-wrote with
Anne-Louise Trividic, based on stories by Hanif Kureishi (who also wrote a novel of the same title).
It stars Kerry Fox and Mark Rylance.
The film is an international co-production between France, the United Kingdom, Germany
and Italy, featuring a soundtrack of pop songs from the 1970s and 1980s.
Intimacy contains an unsimulated fellatio scene by Fox on Rylance.
A French-dubbed version features voice actors
Jean-Hugues Anglade and Nathalie Richard.
The film has been associated with the New French Extremity.
The film explores themes of hotel room, bartender, new french extremism, sex.
The tone is emotional.